let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is the purpose of attribute selectors in CSS?",
        answer: "B. To apply styles to HTML elements with particular attributes",
        options: [
            "A. To select elements based on their name tags",
            "B. To apply styles to HTML elements with particular attributes",
            "C. To target elements with particular class names",  
            "D. None of the above" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which CSS rule will select all paragraph elements with a lang attribute?.",
        answer: "A. p[lang]",
        options: [
            "A. p[lang]",
            "B. p[language]", 
            "C. paragraph[lang]",
            "D. paragraph.lang"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "The attribute selector p[lang l=”en”] is used for:",
        answer: "C. Selects all paragraphs with lang attribute beginning with “en-”",
        options: [
            "A. Selects all paragraphs with lang attribute containing “en” ", 
            "B. Selects all paragraphs with lang attribute has a value of exactly to “en” ", 
            "C. Selects all paragraphs with lang attribute beginning with “en-”", 
            "D. Selects all paragraphs with any lang attributes " 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "The attribute selector p[lang~=”fr”] is used for:",
        answer: "B. Selects all paragraphs with lang attribute containing the word “fr”",
        options: [
            "A. Selects all paragraphs with lang attribute has a value of exactly to “fr”",
            "B. Selects all paragraphs with lang attribute containing the word “fr”",
            "C. Selects all paragraphs with lang attribute beginning with “fr”",
            "D. Selects all paragraphs with any lang attributes"

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "The attribute selector p[lang=”fr”] is used for:",
        answer: "A. Selects all paragraph with lang attribute has a value of exactly to “fr”",
        options: [
            "A. Selects all paragraph with lang attribute has a value of exactly to “fr”", 
            "B. Selects all paragraph with lang attribute containing “fr” ", 
            "C. Selects all paragraph with lang attribute beginning with “fr” ", 
            "D. Selects all paragraph with any lang attributes" 

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "When defining multiple style rules for a single element, how are property and value pairs separated?",
        answer: "C. With a semicolon",
        options: [
            "A. With a comma", 
            "B.With a colon", 
            "C. With a semicolon", 
            "D. With a hyphen" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "If you want to apply a style rule to  h1 , h2 , and  h3  elements, how would you write the selectors?",
        answer: "B. h1, h2, h3",
        options: [
            "A. h1 & h2 & h3", 
            "B. h1, h2, h3", 
            "C. h1 > h2 > h3", 
            "D. h1 / h2 / h3" 

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What is the purpose of grouping selectors in CSS?",
        answer: "C. To apply a style to multiple selectors with the same rule",
        options: [
            "A. To apply styles to HTML elements with particular attributes",
            "B. To limit the numbers of elements styled",
            "C. To apply a style to multiple selectors with the same rule",
            "D. All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Group selectors are separate the selectors with:",
        answer: "B. Commas",
        options: [
            "A. Semicolon",
            "B. Commas",
            "C. Colon",
            "D. Hyphen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What is the purpose of multiple style rules? ",
        answer: "A. To combine multiple properties and corresponding values into a single block",
        options: [
            "A. To combine multiple properties and corresponding values into a single block", 
            "B. You can apply a style to many selectors if you like", 
            "C. To apply styles to HTML elements with particular attributes", 
            "D. None of the above"            

        ]
    },
]